[516-806-4382](tel:516-806-4382) [Book Now](javascript:void(0);)

Rest Easy Pest Control
======================

Website Privacy Policy
----------------------

* * *

### 1\. General

We know that your privacy is important to you, and we work hard to earn and keep your trust. Rest Easy Pest Control (collectively with its subsidiaries, “Company,” “we,” “us,” and “our,”), respects your privacy and is committed to protecting your privacy through our compliance with this Privacy Policy (the “Policy”).

This Policy describes:

* The types of information we collect from you or that you may provide when you visit our website available at: [https://resteasypestcontrol.com](https://www.resteasypestcontrol.com/ "Rest Easy Pest Control Services") as well as any websites and blogs directly owned by the Company where this Policy is linked (collectively, our “Website”).  
* Our practices for collecting, using, maintaining, protecting, and disclosing that information.

This Policy applies to information we collect on this Website or in emails and other electronic messages between you and this Website, and information gathered when you interact with our advertising on third-party websites if such advertisements include links to this Policy.

This Policy does not apply to information collected by us offline or through any other means, including on any other website operated by the Company or any third party, or information collected by any third party through any application or content (including advertising) that may link to or be accessible from the Website (for further information, see below, “Third-party Websites”).

Please read this Policy carefully to understand our practices regarding your information and how we will treat it. If you do not agree with our policies and practices, then please do not use our Website. By using our Website, you agree to the terms of this Policy. This Policy may change from time to time (see below, “Changes to this Policy”). Your continued use of our Website after we make changes is deemed to be acceptance of those changes, so please check the Policy periodically for updates.

* * *

### 2\. What We Collect and How We Collect It

To ensure that we provide you with the best possible experience, we will store, use, and share personal information about you in accordance with this Policy. Personal information is information that identifies, relates to, describes, references, is reasonably capable of being associated with, or could reasonably be linked, directly or indirectly, with a particular user, household or device (“Personal Information”). In particular, the Website may collect the following categories of Personal Information from users of the Website:

| Category | Examples | Collected |
| --- | --- | --- |
| Identifiers | First and last name, postal address, Internet Protocol address, email address, and phone number. | YES |
| Commercial information | Records and photos of personal property, products or services purchased, obtained, or considered, or other purchasing or consuming histories or tendencies. | YES |
| Internet or other similar network activity | Browsing history, search history, information on a consumer's interaction with a website, application, or advertisement. | YES |
| Geolocation data | Physical location or movements. | YES |
| Professional or employment-related information | Current or past job history, including your resume. | YES |

We obtain the categories of Personal Information listed above from the following categories of sources:

* Directly from you . For example, when you:
    * interact with the scheduling feature (i.e. schedule a service);
    * interact with the chat feature;
    * subscribe to one of our e-newsletters;
    * review or comment on one of our products or services;
    * submit a job application;
    * submit other web forms; or
    * otherwise communicate with us, such as request information.
* Indirectly from you . For example, through information we collect from you in the course of providing our services to you.
* Directly and indirectly from activity on our Website . For example, from Website usage details that are collected automatically. For more information on automatic information collection, please review the “Automated Information Collection” section below.

The information that you provide in each case will vary. In some cases, you may be able to provide Personal Information via email or free text boxes, such as contacting the Company to request further information or using the Chat with Us feature on the Website. When providing your Personal Information, please provide only relevant information and do not provide unnecessary sensitive information, such as Social Security numbers, credit card information or other sensitive personal data, unless required for our services.

* * *

### 3\. Automated Information Collection

In addition to the information that you provide to us, we may also collect information about you during your visit to our Website. We collect this information using automated tools that are detailed below. These tools may collect information about your behavior and your computer system, such as your internet address (IP Address), the pages you have viewed, and the actions you have taken while using the Website. Some of the tools we use to automatically collect information about you may include:

* (a) Cookies . A “cookie” is a small data file transmitted from a website to your device’s hard drive. Cookies are usually defined in one of two ways, and we may use either (or both) of them:
    
    * (1) session cookies, which do not stay on your device after you close your browser, and
    * (2) persistent cookies, which remain on your device until you delete them or they expire.
    * We may use the following categories of cookies on our Website.
    
    1. **Strictly Necessary Cookies.** These cookies are essential in order to enable you to move around the Website and use its features. Without these cookies, services you have requested cannot be provided.
    2. **Performance Cookies.** These cookies collect anonymous information on how you use our Website to help us understand how you arrive at our Website, browse or use our Website and highlight areas where we can improve, such as navigation. The data stored by these cookies never shows personal details from which your individual identity can be established.
    3. **Functionality Cookies.** These cookies remember the choices you make such as your preferred language and your search parameters. This information can then be used to provide you with an experience more appropriate to your selections and to make your visits to our Website more tailored to your preferences. The information in these cookies may be anonymized. These cookies cannot track your browsing activity on other websites.
    4. **Targeting Cookies or Advertising Cookies.** These cookies collect information about your browsing habits in order to make advertising more relevant to you and your interests. They are also used to limit the number of times you see an advertisement as well as help measure the effectiveness of an advertising campaign. The cookies are usually placed by third-party advertising networks. These cookies remember the websites you visit and that information is shared with other parties, such as advertisers.

Of course, if you do not wish to have cookies on your devices, you may turn them off at any time by modifying your internet browser’s settings. However, by disabling cookies on your device, you may be prohibited from full use of the Website’s features or lose access to some functionality.

* (b) Google Analytics . The Website sends aggregated non-Personal Information to Google Analytics for the purpose of providing us with the ability to conduct technical and statistical analysis on the Website’s performance. For more information on how Google Analytics supports the Website and uses information sent from the Website, please review Google’s privacy policy available at [https://policies.google.com/technologies/partner-sites](https://policies.google.com/technologies/partner-sites "Google Analytics Properties") .
* (c) Facebook Pixel . With the help of the Facebook pixel, Facebook is on the one hand able to determine the visitors of our online offer as a target group for the presentation of advertisements (so-called "Facebook ads"). Accordingly, we use the Facebook pixel to display our Facebook ads only to Facebook users who have shown an interest in our website or who have specific characteristics (e. g. interests in certain topics or products determined by the websites visited) that we submit to Facebook. With the help of the Facebook pixel, we also want to make sure that our Facebook ads are in line with the potential interest of users and do not have a nuisance effect. Using the Facebook pixel, we can also track the effectiveness of Facebook ads for statistical and market research purposes by seeing whether users have been redirected to our website after clicking on a Facebook ad. Facebook's processing of the data is governed by Facebooks Data Usage Policy. Accordingly, general instructions on how to display Facebook ads is located in the Facebook Data Usage policy https://www.facebook.com/policy.php. For specific information and details about the Facebook pixel and how it works, please visit: https://www.facebook.com/business/help/742478679120153?id=1205376682832142
* (d) Web Beacons . A Web Beacon is an electronic image. Web Beacons can track certain things from your computer and can report activity back to a web server allowing us to understand some of your behavior. If you choose to receive emails from us, we may use Web Beacons to track your reaction to our emails. We may also use them to track if you click on the links and at what time and date you do so. Some of the third-party marketers we engage with may use Web Beacons to track your interaction with online advertising banners on our Website. This information is only collected in aggregate form and will not be linked to your Personal Information. Please note that any image file on a webpage can act as a Web Beacon.
* (e) Embedded Web Links . Links provided in our emails and, in some cases, on third-party websites may include tracking technology embedded in the link. The tracking is accomplished through a redirection system. The redirection system allows us to understand how the link is being used by email recipients. Some of these links will enable us to identify that you have personally clicked on the link and this may be attached to the Personal Information that we hold about you. This data is used to improve our service to you and to help us understand the performance of our marketing campaigns.
* (f) Third-party Websites and Services . We work with a number of service providers of marketing communications technology. These service providers may use various data collection methods to improve the performance of the marketing campaigns we are contracting them to provide. The information collected can be gathered on our Website and also on the websites where our marketing communications are appearing. For example, we may collect data where our banner advertisements are displayed on third-party websites.

* * *

### How We Use Your Information

The information we gather and that you provide is collected to provide you information and the services you request, in addition to various other purposes, including, but not limited to:

* providing the information, products and services you request;
* security, credit or fraud prevention purposes;
* providing you with effective customer service;
* providing you with a personalized experience when you use this Website;
* contacting you with special offers and other information we believe will be of interest to you (in accordance with any privacy preferences you have expressed to us);
* contacting you with information and notices related to your use of this Website;
* inviting you to participate in surveys and providing feedback to us (in accordance with any privacy preferences you have expressed to us);
* better understanding your needs and interests;
* improving the content, functionality and usability of this Website;
* improving our products and services;
* improving our marketing and promotional efforts; and any other purpose identified in an applicable privacy notice, click-through agreement or other agreement between you and us.

Duration . The length of time the Company intends to retain any Personal Information, including any sensitive personal information, is for as long as reasonably necessary to carry out the Company’s intended business purpose for such information.

* * *

### How We Share Your Information

We do not sell or lease your Personal Information to any third party . We may share your Personal Information by disclosing it to a third party for a business purpose. When we disclose your Personal Information, we enter into a contract that describes the purpose and requires the recipient to both keep that Personal Information confidential and not use it for any purpose except for the purposes set forth in the contract.

We disclose your Personal Information for a business purpose to the following categories of third parties:

* Our affiliates; and
* Third party vendors who provide services that enhance our Website, products and services to you (such as vendors for credit card processing, advertising and marketing, and customer support).

Except as described in this Policy, we will not share your information with third parties without your notice and consent, unless it is under one of the following circumstances:

* Legal Reasons.
    * We believe that disclosure is reasonably necessary to comply with any applicable law, regulation, subpoena, or court order;
    * To respond to duly authorized information requests from law enforcement or other governmental authorities;
    * To enforce our agreements and policies;
    * To investigate and prevent security threats, fraud, or other malicious activity; or
    * To respond to an emergency that we believe in good faith requires us to disclose such information to assist in preventing the death or serious bodily injury of any person or Company employee.
* Sale of Business or Merger . There are circumstances where the Company may decide to buy, sell, or reorganize its business in selected countries. Under these circumstances, it may be necessary to share or receive Personal Information with prospective or actual partners or affiliates. In such circumstances, the Company will ensure your information is used in accordance with this Policy.

* * *

### Your Choices and Selecting Your Privacy Preferences

We want to provide you with relevant information that you have requested. When possible, we will always provide options as to what information we collect and how you can manage any preferences that pertains to such information.

If we provide subscription-based services, such as email newsletters, we will allow you to make choices about what information you provide at the point of information collection or at any time after you have received a communication from us while you are subscribed. Transactional or service-oriented messages, such as delivery confirmation messages, are usually excluded from such preferences, as such messages are required to respond to your requests or to provide goods and services, and are not intended for the purposes of marketing.

We will not intentionally send you email newsletters and marketing emails unless you consent to receive such marketing information. After you request to receive these emails, you may opt out of them at any time by selecting the “unsubscribe” link at the bottom of each email. Please note that by opting out or unsubscribing you may affect other services you have requested we provide to you, in which email communication is a requirement of the service provided.

* * *

### Text Messaging

You may have the opportunity to receive SMS or "text" messages, pre-recorded voice messages or auto-dialed phone calls from the Company, its affiliates and related entities as well as third parties. Such messaging may be used to authenticate your identity or mobile device, as well as provide you informational updates about services or products you may have requested. In providing your mobile device number or cell phone number to the Company, you knowingly consent to such communications from the Company or for the Company to use your cell phone number or mobile device number in accordance with the Company’s Terms of Use. In providing your number, you represent that you have the authority to agree to receive text messages at the telephone number that you provide to the Company, or from which you sent the text message request to us. You further acknowledge that no purchase is required to opt into this service, and you may opt out at any time by following the instructions provided in our communications to you.

Any such communications you receive from us will be administered in accordance with your preferences and this Policy.

* * *

### Accuracy and Access to Your Personal Information

We strive to maintain and process your information accurately. We have processes in place to maintain all of our information in accordance with relevant data governance frameworks and legal requirements. We employ technologies designed to help us maintain information accuracy on input and processing.

To view and change the Personal Information that you have provided to us, you can contact us directly for assistance.

* * *

### Information of Minors

We do not intentionally seek to gather information from individuals under the age of eighteen (18). We do not target the Website to minors, and would not expect them to be engaging with our Website or services. We encourage parents and guardians to provide adequate protection measures to prevent minors from providing information unwillingly on the internet. If we are aware of any Personal Information that we have collected about minors, we will take steps to securely remove it from our systems.

* * *

### Submissions

We welcome inquiries or feedback on the services or products you might use or like to use. Any inquiries, feedback, suggestions, ideas, materials, comments or other information you provide to us (collectively, “Submissions”) will be treated as non-proprietary and non-confidential. Your Submissions on or through this Website, such as reviews, may be available to others who visit this Website. In addition, we may use your Submissions in advertising campaigns and other promotions. We may or may not use your name in connection with such use, and we may or may not seek your consent before using the Submissions for such purposes. Therefore, you should have no expectation of privacy with respect to your Submissions on or through this Website. You should not submit any content you do not wish to make available to the general public. In particular, your Submissions must not violate the privacy or other rights of others. You may not use false identifying information or contact information, impersonate any person or entity, or otherwise mislead us as to the origin of any Submission.

* * *

### Third-party Websites

This Policy does not apply to websites or other domains that are maintained or operated by third parties or our affiliates. Our Website may link to third-party websites and services. For example, if you click on an advertisement on this Website, you may be taken to another website that we do not control. These links are not endorsements of these websites, and this Policy does not extend to them. Because this Policy is not enforced on these third-party websites, we encourage you to read any posted privacy policy of the third-party website before using the service or website and providing any information.

* * *

### Your California Rights

Shine the Light law . Pursuant to California Civil Code Section 1798.83, we will not disclose or share your Personal Information with third parties for the purposes of third-party marketing to you without your prior consent.

Do Not Track Signals . Other than as disclosed in this Policy, the Website does not track users over time and across third-party websites to provide targeted advertising. Therefore, the Website does not operate any differently when it receives Do Not Track (“DNT”) signals from your internet web browser.

WE DO NOT SELL OR SHARE YOUR PERSONAL INFORMATION . If we ever decide to sell or share Personal Information, as those terms are defined under the California Consumer Privacy Act of 2018, we will update you via this Policy and include a link entitled “Do Not Sell or Share My Personal Information,” to provide you with an opportunity to opt out of the selling or sharing of your Personal Information.

California Consumer Rights . If you are a California consumer, as defined by the California Consumer Privacy Act of 2018 (“Act”), please be advised that Any Hour, LLC, does not currently meet the regulatory thresholds of a “business” as that term is defined under the Act and therefore is not required to comply with the Act. Regardless, all Personal Information will be processed in accordance with this Policy.

* * *

### For Website Visitors Outside of the United States

Our Website is designed for use by individuals in the United States only. We do not warrant or represent that this Policy or the Website’s use of your Personal Information complies with the laws of any other jurisdiction. Furthermore, to provide you with our services, we may store, process, and transmit information in the United States and other locations around the world, including countries that may not have the same privacy and security laws as yours. Regardless of the country in which such information is stored, we will process your Personal Information in accordance with this Policy.

* * *

### Safeguarding the Information We Collect

We use reasonable technical, administrative, and physical safeguards in order to protect your Personal Information against accidental loss and from unauthorized access, use, alteration, and disclosure. However, we can never promise 100% security. If you ever feel your information has been compromised or is at risk, please notify us via the How to Contact Us section below.

* * *

### Changes to this Policy

This Policy describes our current policies and practices with regard to the information we collect through this Website. We are continually improving and adding to the features and functionality of this Website along with the products and services we offer through this Website. If we make any changes to this Policy, a revised Policy will be posted on this webpage and the date of the change will be reported in the “Last Revised” block above. You can get to this page from any of our webpages by clicking on the “Privacy Policy” link (usually at the bottom of the screen).

* * *

### How to Contact Us

We value your opinions and welcome your feedback. To contact us about this Policy or your Personal Information, please contact us.

You can Rest Easy Contact us for a free Quote
---------------------------------------------

[Call Us

Call](tel:516-806-4382 "Call Rest Easy Pest Control")

[Send Message

Message](https://www.resteasypestcontrol.com/about/contact "Contact Rest Easy Pest Control")

Book Now

Book

40 Glen St Suite B  
Glen Cove, New York 11542

Give Us A Call!

Hours

Mon - Sat: 7:00am - 7:00pm

[

### Easy Online Booking

 Book Now](javascript:void(0);)

© 2024 Rest Easy Pest Control | All Rights Reserved | [Sitemap](https://www.resteasypestcontrol.com/sitemap) | [Privacy Policy](https://www.resteasypestcontrol.com/privacy-policy) | [Accessibility](https://www.resteasypestcontrol.com/accessibility) | Digital Marketing By [Ninthroot](https://ninthroot.com/)

##### Book Now

Please ensure Javascript is enabled for purposes of [website accessibility](https://userway.org/)
